uquiz.com 2019-01-03

# uQuiz.com - Free Online Quiz Maker for your Website or Blog

## Collection of Information and where it comes from

We collect information, including personally-identifiable information. The information that is collected depends on the function(s) that are being performed. You can always choose not to provide information to us, but this may mean that you are unable to access any or all features offered on our website. We try, wherever reasonably possible, to keep the amount and types of information collected to only what is required to perform the services provided by our website.

### If you access our services:

  * #### Personal Information

You might provide us with your contact information such as: your name and email address. This may be provided through a form on our website, when registering for a user account, when interacting with us via our contact form, email or social media. 
  * #### Device and Browser Information

We collect information about the device, machine and application you use to access our services. Device data mainly means your IP address, operating system version, device type, system and performance information, and browser type. 

### If you register for an account:

  * #### Registration Information

When you register for an account, we collect your first and last name, username, email address and password. If you choose to register using Facebook or assocate your Facebook account with your uQuiz account, then we also collect your Facebook user id. 
  * #### Paid Subscription and Payment Information

If you subscribe to our paid subscription service, we collect and store information relating to your paid subscription to our service including your payment history, products and services you’ve ordered, payment details as provided either by you via a form on our website or as received by us through communications to our third-party payment providers regarding a contract or payment agreement. This information includes: your name, your address, email address, payer identifier, transaction identifier and agreement identifier.

We make use of Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software to protect and encrypt information that is submitted to us as part of online card payment transactions. We use third party mechanisms for transaction processing and subsequently we do not store credit card information on our own website or servers.

  * #### User Generated Content and Uploads

Information and uploads to our website which is provided by you when creating user generated content, such as quizzes. This may be provided by you through a form on our website. 
  * #### Account Settings

You might provide us with information to personalise your experience of the services that we provide. This may include your communication preferences and a timezone for your account. 

### If you take a quiz:

The vast majority of the quizzes on our website are created by users of our quiz maker. By taking a quiz on our website you acknowledge and agree that any information, including personally-identifiable information is collected and stored on behalf of the quiz creator and is made available to the quiz creator through their account, in real-time and in downloadable form. Quiz responses remain anonymous unless you voluntarily provide personally identifiable information.

  * #### Personal Information

You might voluntarily provide personal information before, during and after taking a quiz. The types of information that is collected is defined by the quiz creator and will differ from quiz to quiz. Information collected as part of the quiz taking process is collected and processed by us on behalf of the quiz creator. 
  * #### Quiz responses

When you take a quiz, your responses are collected on behalf of the quiz creator, this may include but is not limited to the name provided at the start of the quiz, the answers you provided, fill in the blank values entered, the time taken to answer each question, your final result and the quiz as a whole. 

## Data Retention

We will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.

To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.

## International Transfers

We may transfer your personal information outside of the European Economic Area. This will be as a result of our service and infrastructure providers being based outside of this area, such as our host Amazon Web Services.

## Sharing of Information

We will not rent or sell personally-identifiable information that has been collected as part of the services that we provide to any third party. We will however disclose any information that we deem is appropriate in order to comply with the law, enforce our policies, protect our rights, property or safety of uQuiz, our users or others.

## Use of Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of information that is stored in the browser by a website that the browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. We use cookies in order to identify users, track visitors, their usage of our websites and their website access preferences. Visitors that do not wish to accept cookies from uQuiz should, before they access the uQuiz website, set their browser to refuse cookies. Due to the nature of our website, most of the functionality requires the use of cookies in order to function correctly, so this may prevent such features from working.

In order to gain insights into our users and improve the services that we provide, we make use of Google Analytics features such as Audience Demographics and Interests Reporting. In order to collect the information required for these features, we use the first-party Google Analytics Cookie. If you wish to opt out of Google Analytics data collection, you may go so by downloading the opt-out browser add-in developed by Google at the following link [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

## Transfer of Business

If uQuiz were acquired, went out of business or becomes bankrupt, the information collected as part of any services that we provide on our website, including user information, would be included in the assets that would be transferred to a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and that the receiving party may continue to use your personal information in accordance to this Privacy Policy.

## Changes to Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is subject to change at the sole discretion of uQuiz and we encourage all users to return back to this page on a regular basis. If you continue to use uQuiz after a change to this Privacy Policy, this constitutes your acceptance of the changes.
